(Leonard:)We think we can help you
with your stage fright.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I doubt that.
(Sheldon:)I haven't figured out a way
and I'm much smarter than all of you.
(Penny:)Yes, but you're not smarter
than all of us put together.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm sorry.
That is what I meant.
(Penny:)Okay. Your problem is
you're trying to do this all by yourself.
We could help you.
We can be your team.
Like Professor Xavier
and his X-Men.
(Sheldon:)I do like the X-Men.
(Penny:)Did I see X-Men?
(Leonard:)Yeah, we watched it last week.
You said you liked it.
(Penny:)Oh, I say a lot of things, sweetie.
(Penny:)So how about it, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)I don't know. If you're my X-Men,
what are your powers?
Okay, well, I'm gonna take you
shopping, get you a nice suit.
(Penny:)-Might give you more confidence.
-It's not exactly a mutation...
(Sheldon:)...that would get you into Xavier's
School for Gifted Youngsters...
(Sheldon:)...but go on. Leonard?